The next project we're going to show you for Mother's Day, is some rub-ons that you can use with little glass vases.
Rub-ons are really hot right now, and here's one that I've done.
This is called an old olive color, and I've just rubbed it onto this cute little vase.
Here's some other things you can do.
This is a votive holder.
This one also has rub-ons.
Here's a little jar, this one also has rub-ons.
I've just tied it with a ribbon.
This would be really cute with some cotton balls in it, if you used it in the bathroom.
Q-tips, any small little thing that you want to put.
And here's a nice little mug, with some rub-ons.
So, let's get started.
The first thing I'm going to do is, choose what I want to rub on.
So I'm going to go ahead and use this chocolate chip, and there's this really pretty butterfly, so.
Because it's in a little bit, I'm going to go ahead and cut it out.
If it was closer to the edge, I could just lift up the paper, and slide it in.
And then you just want to make sure that your glass is clean and dry.
And, I've already done that.
So, I've taken my butterfly, and I'm just going to press it here.
A couple things you can do here.
I just use kind of the heat from my hand, and kind of push it down.
You could also put a piece of tape there to hold it.
The pack of the rub-ons come with this little Popsicle stick.
You can use that to rub, you could use your bone folder to rub.
I like to use my stylus.
So, now that I have it in place.
And I'm just going to turn it, and hold it down flat, and I'm just going to go ahead and rub.
And you're just going to rub, and you'll see, as you're rubbing, that the color on your, what you're embossing, is going to lighten, as it's applied to the glass.
So you just keep rubbing, and rubbing, until you see it lifting.
And then you can go ahead and push with your thumb, and you can see, I'll need a little bit more there.
And then just go ahead and gradually lift it off.
If it's not ready to come, just give it another rub.
Sometimes it takes a little time, but just be patient.
And then when you lift it off at the end, you will have a beautiful butterfly rub-on to your glass vase.
And when you come back, I'll show you what else you can do with these.